Let's investigate the X-field file from the machine.
So we have X-field32.txt file through the R1.
So there is database that will store all these kinds of network usage.
The data base will be present under the C Windows system 32.
There is a folder called S-U.
Let me see where it is here, here we have.
So here we can find S-R-U-D-B dot is dot V-8, okay?
System resource usage or database, okay?
So the first form is system resource usage data base, it will store all the resource
usage like application usage, network usage, network connections and CPU usage, a lot
of things, okay?
We need to investigate this S-R-U-D-B dot-D-8 and let me copy this file and let me put
it in and I'll create a folder and put in S-R-U, okay?
So let's move towards one of the tool called Eric Cimmerman tool, Eric Cimmerman tool.
So here we can find a lot of foreign six tools here, so we are going to choose S-R-U-Sum-E-B,
sorry, yeah, some data, sorry, S-R-U-Sum-E-C-M-D, okay?
And let's open this and let's push this file into this directory, let's move to let's
do this and here we have, let's see how to move this and here you can find this and
for example, to use this tool, okay, let's execute this S-R-E-C-F and we need to give the
data base file, that's the C-S-V and we can store the C-S-V in the same, okay?
So if it was done and we can see plenty of, we can see plenty of Excel sheets, C-S-E-C-Files,
we got from the S-R-V data, okay, we're including push notification, energy usage, application
timeline provider, application resources usage, network usage.
So currently I don't have the Excel sheet here, so I'll be moving to my primary machine
to get a help from the Excel, let's draw a hand drop, the network usage, cell sheet and
let's investigate that, so this is the one, yeah, and we know the threat attack is used
R-Clone for exfiltration, so let me filter it with the R-Clone and see how this happened,
okay, now we can understand, there is bytes sent and bytes is used, right?
So 14, 737, 520, so issue, convert this sent to Google bytes to any, so it's, it was
saying 14 megabytes of data get transformed into the cloud application, right?
So we exfilled the file from, where it is, where we collected the file, see user's
public, if you see this, this file is also saying 14 megabytes of data, right, so we can
understand from here, so this file get, from 14 megabytes of data get exfilled data to
through R-Clone.exe on the date and the time, right?
So this is how you can do some kind of foreign 16 cube inside the machine and you can find
out what actually happened, how much data get exfilled data, okay, you can track the data,
how much data get exfilled it, let's take out the network connection logs, okay, we can't
able to see any other data from here, let's dig something,
it's an resource usage, this application has to start, and it has to be embedded, so this
was used to buy, this user, this user said, right, this is the SAD of the user's security
identifier, let's move to the game, let's use the user.
this is the same SAD of the user head, so we need to find out this who exfilled the file
into the cloud platform, so this is important, we check, okay, because we are going to do
some kind of response actions from this collected information, okay, let's hop off from
here we'll continue our discussion in the next video, see you guys, bye.